rodatabase.net 2017-06-11

# Items - Revelation Online Database

**WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

**How Black Desert Database uses Your Personal Information**  
This policy covers how Black Desert Database treats personal information that Black Desert Database collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Black Desert Database products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This privacy policy only applies to Black Desert Database  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Black Desert Database does not own or control, or to people that Black Desert Database does not employ or manage.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
Black Desert Database collects personal information when you register with Black Desert Database, when you use Black Desert Database products or services.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. When you register with Black Desert Database and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Black Desert Database collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.

Black Desert Database automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Black Desert Database cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

Black Desert Database uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
Black Desert Database does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process(such as law enforcement requests), or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Black Desert Database's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
We transfer information about you if Black Desert Database is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Black Desert Database will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
Black Desert Database displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

Black Desert Database does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

**COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES**  
Black Desert Database may set and access Black Desert Database cookies on your computer. We may also set and access device identifiers which could include IP address, user agent information (browser version, OS type and version), and device provided identifiers.

Black Desert Database lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies and device identifiers is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Black Desert Database's cookies.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  
You can edit your Black Desert Database Account Information at any time. You can also modify information you have provided to Black Desert Database through the Black Desert Database products or services you may use.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Black Desert Database service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Black Desert Database Newsletter, that are considered part of your Black Desert Database account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

If you wish to delete your Black Desert Database account, ask us via e-mail or PM on our forum.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
Black Desert Database may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Black Desert Database account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**QUESTION AND SUGGESTIONS**  
If you have questions, suggestions, or wish to make a complaint you can contact us via PM on our forum.
